Finding aid for the R.B. Kitaj papers LSC.1741
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 5. Personal Objects and Memorabilia, 1964-2007; 9 boxes
  This series includes various materials and objects associated with Kitaj's personal life, including family memorabilia, calendars, photographs, itineraries, and other materials.
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Business cards, undated (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Collected Materials and Objects
    - Post Cards, no date (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Yearbook, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Medical clippings, 1973 - 1998 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Travel clippings, 1978 - 1984 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Ceremonial sash, undated (Box 138, Folder 34)
    - Mementos, 1981 - 1994 (Box 139, Folder 36)
    - Mementos -- 1960s (1 of 4), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Mementos -- 1960s (2 of 4), Undated.; 1 item. (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Mementos -- 1960s (3 of 4), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Mementos -- 1960s (4 of 4), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (1 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (2 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (3 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (4 of 10) (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (5 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (6 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (7 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (8 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (9 of 10) (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Mementos -- 1960s - 1970s (10 of 10), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Mementi -- 1977 (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Mementi -- 1977 (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Mementos, undated (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Mementos -- 1980s (1 of 5) (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Mementos -- 1980s (2 of 5), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Mementos -- 1980s (3 of 5), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Mementos -- 1980s (4 of 5), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Mementos -- 1980s (5 of 5), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Mementos -- 1990s (1 of 6) (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Mementos -- 1990s (2 of 6), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Mementos -- 1990s (3 of 6), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Mementos -- 1990s (4 of 6), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Mementos -- 1990s (5 of 6), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Mementos -- 1990s (6 of 6) (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Past and Memorabilia (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Past and Memorabilia (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Materials brought from Kitaj's house, 1980 - 1986 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Kitaj Obituaries (1 of 2), 2007 - 2008 (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Kitaj's Last Bag (1 of 2) (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Kitaj's Last Bag (2 of 2), undated (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Mounted photograph, undated (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Wall calendar -- 1990 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Family and Friends
    - Baby slippers and piece of hair, no date (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Tracey Emin -- handkerchief, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 25)
    - Joe Shannon -- letter to Kitaj family, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 26)
    - David Hockney (1 of 2), 1963 - 2006 (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - David Hockney (2 of 2), 1977 - 2000 (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Lem Dobbs (1 of 9), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - Lem Dobbs (2 of 9) (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - Lem Dobbs (3 of 9), 1989 (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - Lem Dobbs (4 of 9), 1990 (Box 140, Folder 20)
    - Lem Dobbs (5 of 9), 1991 (Box 140, Folder 21)
    - Lem Dobbs (6 of 9), 1992 (Box 140, Folder 22)
    - Lem Dobbs (7 of 9) (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Dick and Betsy Smith, 1966 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Lem Dobbs (8 of 9), 1984, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Lem Dobbs (9 of 9), 1984, 1992 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Ethel Fisher, 2006 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Robert Duncan -- obituary (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Personal Documents
    - Calendars, itineraries, and addresses, ca. 1975 - 2003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Financial notebook, 1990 - 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - House Materials, 1964 - 1965 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - House Materials (1 of 3), 1966 - 1985 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - House Materials (2 of 3) (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - House Materials (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - House (1 of 3), 1978 - 1997 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - House (2 of 3), 1974 - 1980 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - House (3 of 3), 1974 - 1980 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Legal -- Heydons (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Legal, 1966 - 1975 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Financial Matters (1 of 2), 1970 - 1979 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Financial Matters (2 of 2), 1970 - 1979 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Financial, 1968 - 2007 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Financial notebook (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Financial notebook, 1977 - 1979 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Financial notebook, 1985 - 1991 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Financial clippings, 1994 - 1997 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Medical materials, 1998 - 2007 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Medical materials and clippings (1 of 2) (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Medical materials and clippings (2 of 2), 1980 - 1996 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - House Materials, 1977 - 1985 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - House Materials, 1987 - 1998 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Annotated Calendar Pages, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Voter and Vehicle Registration (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Nanny Matters, 1985 - 1991 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Addresses (1 of 3), 1973 - 1990 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Addresses (2 of 3), undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Addresses (3 of 3), undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Mailing and Invitation Lists (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Mailing and Invitation Lists, 1994 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Mailing and Invitation Lists, 1990 - 1994 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Mailing and Invitation Lists, undated (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Contract for Alterations and Extensions -- 62 Elm Park Road, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Contract for Alterations and Extensions -- 62 Elm Park Road, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Architectural plans -- 62 Elm Park Road (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Architectural plans -- 62 Elm Park Road (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Architectural plans -- 62 Elm Park Road (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Clause 28 letter campaign (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Clause 28 letter campaign (2 of 2) (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Clause 28 letter campaign (1 of 1), 1988 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Sandra Fisher -- obituary, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Almeida Theatre Company, 1995 (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - Sandra Fisher obituary and related materials, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Ashes on the Sea memorial certificates (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - Jeanne Kitaj memorial pamphlet, 1995 (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Passports, identification cards, certificates, 1951 - 1975 (Box 132, Folder 27)
    - Troy, Ohio -- maps and photographs, 1950 - 1976 (Box 132, Folder 40)
    - Address Book pages, undated (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Business Cards (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Diplomas from Humanity Research Center of Beverly Hills, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 25)
    - Address and telephone books, undated; 2 items. (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Marlborough Galleries Diaries, 1991, 1992, 1994; 3 items. (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Red sketchbook, undated; 1 item. (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Ryman Diary, 1973, Undated. (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Tate Gallery Diary, 1974, Undated. (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Planner, 1975, Undated. (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Tate Gallery Diary, 1976, Undated. (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Tate Gallery Diary, 1977, Undated. (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Tate Gallery Diary, 1980 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Tate Gallery Diary, 1982, Undated. (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - House -- design ideas, 1969 - 1978 (Box 165, Folder 12)
  - Photographs
    - Photographs, ca. 1970 -2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and inventory report -- Sam Kitaj, undated (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - The 1853 Gallery, undated (Box 139, Folder 22)
    - Kitaj at Lockheed, undated (Box 139, Folder 23)
    - Gallery photographs, undated (Box 139, Folder 24)
    - Kitaj by J.S. Lewinsky (1 of 2), undated (Box 139, Folder 25)
    - Kitaj by J.S. Lewinsky (2 of 2), undated (Box 139, Folder 26)
    - Robert Duncan and Kitaj (Box 139, Folder 27)
    - Jim Dine, Robert Creeley, Kitaj, undated (Box 139, Folder 28)
    - Kitaj portrait by Lucian Freud, undated (Box 139, Folder 29)
    - Kitaj photograph by John C. Ward, undated (Box 139, Folder 30)
    - Kitaj portraits, undated (Box 139, Folder 31)
    - Kitaj with portrait of Sandra Fisher (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Works by Others
    - Julie Claxton -- photograph, 1998 (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - David Hockney, 1991, 1992; 2 items. (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Jacob Samuel, 1994 (Box 156, Folder 26)
- 6. Materials Collected by R.B. Kitaj, 1959-2007; 17 boxes
  - No Subseries assigned
    - Untitled dissertation, no date (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Unknown document, no date (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 - 2004; 5 items. (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Loose booklet pages, undated (Box 117, Folder 37)
    - The Critic Kills, undated (Box 135, Folder 31)
    - Art History's New Warrior Breed by Sara Day, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 24)
    - After Impressionism: The crisis in Paris in the 1880s -- Proposal for an exhibition, undated (Box 136, Folder 32)
    - Annotated articles, 1984 - 2000 (Box 137, Folder 35)
    - Annotated articles, 1991 - 2000 (Box 137, Folder 36)
    - Annotated articles, 1962 - 2001 (Box 137, Folder 37)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts: Preview (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Ben Uri -- news bulletin, 2005 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture -- donors packet, Undated. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Westminster Synagogue Newsletter (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - The Riverside Arts & Crafts Group, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Church Walk Kensington by Patricia Hutchins, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Robert Creeley, Robert Duncan, and John Ashbery -- lists of works, undated (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Covent Garden, 1974 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - "J.C. Lee, Berggruen, Gray, Goulds, Claude, B.T.", 1984 - 1986 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous invitations (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous invitations, 1967 - 1976 (Box 138, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 138, Folder 33)
    - Dean Brelis report on Vladimir Horowitz (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Dean Brelis report on Vladimir Horowitz (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Articles by and about Gabriel Josipovici (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Anti-Communism and the Sontag Circle by Hilton Kramer, September 1986 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - The Book of the Absent by Edmond Jabes -- excerpt, undated (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Literary Cavalcade Magazine, March 1972 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - In Dreams Begin Responsibilities by Delmore Schwartz, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Presidential Address by Rabbi Alexander M. Schindler (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 139, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1992 - 2003 (Box 145, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1992 - 2003 (Box 145, Folder 19)
    - Announcements and invitations -- various artists, 2004 - 2005 (Box 145, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous -- various artists (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (1 of 2), 1984 - 2007 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (2 of 2), 1984 - 2007 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - The History of the Growth and Decay of The Ottoman Empire -- Demetrius Cantemir, Undated. (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Catherine Deneuve -- Belle de Jour, undated (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Moses lithograph -- proof, 1992 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Clippings and Articles (1 of 2), 1962, 1999 - 2006 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Clippings and Articles (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Art in America, 1976 - 2007 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Art News, 1975 - 2007 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - The Bauhaus - Graphic Design, by Bernard Myers (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Exhibition Documents, Undated. (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles Times Magazine, 2002 - 2003 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975 - 2005 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Modern Painters, 2004 - 2007 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - The New Republic (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - New York Magazine, Apr. 3, 2006 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - The New York Times Magazine, 1995 - 2005 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - The New Yorker, 2003 - 2007 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Newsweek, 1989 - 1995 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Objects and Documents bought by Richard Smith (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Observer Magazine, 1974 - 1979 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Olana House built by Frederic Church, 1983 - 1989 (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Time magazine, 1972 - 2001 (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Mark Rothko & the Rothko case: notes, memories, observations by John Bernard Myers, 1983 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - The Oxford Magazine, 12 March 1959 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Identity and Creativity: The Jew as Artist/Artist as Jew -- Panel discussion transcript, 15 November 1985 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Whistler and His Influence in Britain by David Brown, 1977 (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - Swinging Art Dealers, 1964 (Box 149, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous -- Annotated articles, 1995 - 2000 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (1 of 4) (Box 151, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous (2 of 4), 2002 - 2003 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (3 of 4), 2003 - 2004 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous (4 of 4), 2003 - 2004 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Yale Center for British Art -- brochure, January-April 2004 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Announcements and invitations (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated. (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated. (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous articles, 1992 - 2005 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - City vs. Country: The Rural Image in French Painting From Millet to Gauguin by Dr. Robert L. Herbert, undated (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - The Listener -- magazine, 15 December 1960 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Thirst Magazine -- proof, 2003 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - The Cooper Union --magazine, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland Indians -- bumper sticker, undated (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - A Thousand Years of France -- excerpt, undated (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Father-to-be Warren tries a new role by Peter Holt (Box 153, Folder 25)
    - The New York Times: Book Review, 20 May 1979 (Box 153, Folder 26)
    - Artforum -- miscellaneous, 1997 - 2002 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Artforum -- miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Artforum -- miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Artforum -- miscellaneous (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - The Barons of Bond Street by John Pearson, 17 March 1963 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Gazette, 1961 (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - Art for McGovern -- campaign materials, 1972; 5 items. (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - First Principles, for 19 instruments by Morton Feldman, 1968 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Collector's Netsuke by Raymond Bushell -- clippings and notes, 1993 - 1995 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Julian Rios -- reviews and articles, 1986 - 1987 (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Book covers, undated; 3 items. (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Mounted photographs, undated; 2 items. (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous prints, undated (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Russian publications (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Painting Pretty Pictures sheet music by Johnny Weddell and Mabelle Francis, 1971; 1 item. (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - Mounted photograph, undated; 1 item. (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - Mark Symczak -- original artwork, 1 item. (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - Mounted photograph, undated; 1 item. (Box 187, Folder 14)
    - Depression (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Depression (1 of 2), Undated. (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - God (2 of 2), Undated. (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - National Gallery, Undated. (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Photography (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Russians, Undated. (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - New York Times, 7 March 1965 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Why the R.C.A. is a National Asset by Sir Paul Reilly, 2 November 1967 (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994 - 1999 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Bartolommeo, 1995 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Annotated articles (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 - 2005 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - "The lady really was a tramp" by Stuart Nicholson, 21 July 1996; 1 item. (Box 226, Folder 17)
  - 3. Art Bulletins
    - Allen Memorial Art Museum bulletin (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1994 March, 1996 May (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - National Gallery News bulletin, 1996 July - 1997 March (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - National Gallery News (1 of 4), 1994 - 1995 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - National Gallery News (2 of 4), 1996 - 1997 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - National Gallery News (3 of 4) (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - National Gallery News (4 of 4), 2000 - 2001 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Art Exhibits, Catalogs, and Posters
    - Art in Jewish Culture exhibition catalogue, 1996 April (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Assorted exhibition catalogues, 1986 - 1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Christie's Important Old Master, Modern and Contemporary Prints auction catalogue, 1996 December (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Global Architects (GA) Houses 87 catalogue, 2005 April (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - National Academy of Design 178th annual exhibition catalogue, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Phillips International auction catalogue (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gerard Caris exhibition poster, 1981 March (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Masks catalogue, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Marlborough Contemporary Dialogue, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      1 CD.
      Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - Jim Dine Drawings -- poster, 1966 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - An evening with Edward Lucie-Smith -- poster, 1967 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Irving Petlin -- poster, undated (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits
    - Nationalgalerie paintings catalog, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Sandra Fisher exhibition invitations, 1993 - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Family
    - Lem Dobb's publicity material, 1993 - 1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Family and Friends
    - Lem Dobbs, 1990 - 1992 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Invitations
    - Assorted invitations (1 of 5), ca. 1980 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Assorted invitations (2 of 5), ca. 1980 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Assorted invitations (3 of 5), ca. 1980 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Assorted invitations (4 of 5), ca. 1980 - 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Assorted invitations (5 of 5), ca. 1980 - 2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Announcements and invitations (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1982 - 1983 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Announcements and invitations, 1984 - 1985 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition announcements and invitations, 1960 - 1993 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1970 - 1994 (Box 132, Folder 39)
    - Invitations and announcements (Box 132, Folder 43)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1967 - 1977 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1970 - 1979 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1990 - 1992 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1990 - 1994 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1992 - 1994 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1993 - 1995 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1990 - 1996 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1994 - 1997 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1995 - 1997 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1996 - 1997 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 2001 - 2007 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1992 - 1993 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1966 - 1970 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1981 - 1989 (Box 133)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1960 - 1969 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1970 - 1979 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1980 - 1984 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1985 - 1989 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1990 - 1992 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1993 - 1994 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Invitations and announcements, 1995 - 1999 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Invitations and announcements (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition announcements, 1970 - 1994 (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Photographs
    - Kitajlonia -- photograph albums, undated (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Julian Rios -- portrait, 1989 - 1990 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Collected photographs, undated (Box 139, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Jean Renoir and John Ford, undated (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Works by Others
    - Rabbi Adin Steinsaltz, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - The Secret of the Gentiles by David Plante, undated (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Untitled essay, undated (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Glees, Swarthy Monotonies, Rince Cochon, and Chozzerai for Simon, Poems 1979 by Jonathan Williams, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Ecce Homo by Robert Creeley, undated; 1 item. (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Photographs of Stephen Wilmoth sculptures, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - WhosaJew by J.W. Phillips -- exhibition proposal, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - Unidentified poetry, undated (Box 117, Folder 36)
    - Jimmy Ong: Profane and Sacred, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 38)
    - Robert Sheppard, 1986 - 1987 (Box 117, Folder 40)
    - Mariano Antolin Rato y Julian Rios: Vanguardistas tradicionales, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Auto da Fénix by Julian Rios, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Karnevalen i Larva: om Julian Rios roman by Christian Kupchick, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Julian Rios -- articles and reviews, 1989 - 1991 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Tintin in the New World: A Romance by Frederic Tuten -- draft (1 of 4), 1992 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Tintin in the New World: A Romance by Frederic Tuten -- draft (2 of 4), 1992 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Tintin in the New World: A Romance by Frederic Tuten -- draft (3 of 4), 1992 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Tintin in the New World: A Romance by Frederic Tuten -- draft (4 of 4), 1992 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Jean Lambert Tallien: A Romance by Frederic Tuten, undated (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Crazy About Women: Poems by Paul Durcan -- proof (1 of 4), 1991 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Crazy About Women: Poems by Paul Durcan -- proof (2 of 4), 1991 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Crazy About Women: Poems by Paul Durcan -- proof (3 of 4), 1991 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Crazy About Women: Poems by Paul Durcan -- proof (4 of 4), 1991 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Paintings and Monotypes by Sandra Fisher, 1993 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Sandra Fisher / Days on the Water & Other Pictures, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Santa Cruz Remembers: Lou Harrison -- memorial pamphlet, 2003 (Box 132, Folder 28)
    - Order and Chaos chez Hans Reichel by Henry Miller -- prospectus, undated (Box 132, Folder 31)
    - Paintings by Sylvia Sleigh -- announcement, 1963 (Box 132, Folder 32)
    - Howard Hodgkin: Paintings, 1977 - 84, 1984 (Box 132, Folder 33)